Previously on JoJo's
Bizarre Adventure! Mrs.
Cujo has materialized her own stand!
I'll keep you from Lord Dio
if it's the last thing I do!
But if we fail to find
Dio within 50 days...
Someone I know has a mark.
A birthmark just like this
on the back of their neck.
Know anyone like that?
What?!
If that is true, I must join you
on your trek to Egypt, messieurs!
By going after Dio, I will find
the one who took my sister's life!
Thank you.
The Loathsome Curse of Dio,
even the Speedwagon Foundation's
leading physicians with their
cutting-edge treatments stand
powerless before Dio's curse.
To save Holly, Jojo and crew
continue on their journey to Egypt.
With air travel now too treacherous, they
board a boat heading first to Singapore.
To get from Hong Kong to Singapore, we'll
be on the water for three full days.
Well, let's relax and keep our spirits up.
But first, I have a serious question.
What the hell is with the
high school uniforms, you two?
Can't you go and find
something else to put on?
Isn't it ridiculously hot?
Well, we are students, after all.
And good students should behave
as such no matter where they are.
But I guess that sounds like a stretch.
Hmph. Huh!
Japanese students are
such stiffs, aren't they?
So this is what they call Bushido.
Like they say, clear your mind
and even flames feel cool.
That's all well and good, but that
really won't get you any girls.
Let go!
Let go of me!
Dammit, I said get off of me!
Shut your trap!
What's your problem? Ya
brat! Hey! Who's there?
I thought we agreed there'd be no
other passengers on board but us!
Go! Sorry, sir.
It's a stowaway.
This little brat was hiding in
one of the storage holes below!
Stow away?
What you waiting for?
Come at me!
I'll freaking break your balls!
Tell that to the police, you little shit!
I dare ya! What? The police?
Wait, I'm sorry, alright?
Please, just let me go!
I just wanted to go to Singapore
to see my dad, that's all!
I'll do anything!
You can even put me to work for my ticket!
Let's see, what should I do?
Should I let you go or turn you in?
What to do?
We could use another cabin, boy.
No way I'm letting you go.
That's too easy.
But first, I'm gonna let the captain know.
Whoa, in he goes.
That kid's got guts.
Is he planning to swim
to shore from out here?
What should we do?
Just leave him.
He wouldn't have dived in
if he wasn't a good swimmer.
No, he's in danger!
This entire area is infested with sharks!
This isn't good.
Hey, kids!
There's sharks out there!
No!
Aurora!
Good grief.
Come on, you brat.
Hold on.
A girl and a runty wanted
that. Just my luck. Hey!
How dare you fill me up
like that, you bastard!
It's off!
Good grief, kid.
Hey, Jotaro! Below you!
Something's coming after
you from underwater it's not
a shark and it's Racing
towards you you have to get out
of there now hurry swim to
the boat he's Too far away
if it's at that distance
leave it to my viral fat green
It just disappeared that
thing is a stand stunning
an aquatic stand In all my
dealings with the occult,
I've never heard of such a thing.
This girl, there's no way she's the...
Could she be that Stan's user?
Did she try to lead Jojo into
shark-infested waters on purpose?
Jeez, what's with you jerks?
Stop staring like that, it's creepy.
I have no idea what's going
on here, but I'll fight you!
Don't underestimate me, okay?
You're gonna regret this.
One-on-one, come at me,
I dare you, you punks!
Is she playing us?
Maybe we should toss
her back into the ocean.
Calm down.
If she is just a stowaway and
gets eaten by sharks, it'd be bad.
We've already checked the
ten people on this boat.
I'm positive they're all in the clear.
I don't know who it could
be other than this girl.
Isn't there a way we could
find out who she really is?
Hey, how is Dio doing
these days? Dio, huh?
What the hell is that?
Don't pretend like you
don't know, you little brat.
Hey, I warned you, punks!
You gonna be a man and talk to me?
Or do you just wanna get shanked?
Which is it, huh?
My demon blade wants the
blood of its 340th victim,
and you all look like prime cuts.
Heh.
And...
What's so funny, stupid jerkhole?
Jerkhole?
I'm starting to get the feeling
she's not our stand user.
Yes.
But who then?
This girl our stowaway?
Thanks for grabbing her for me.
Huh?
Whoa, Captain.
I'm pretty strict when it comes
to stowaways on my ship here.
You may be a girl, but if I go easy on you,
we'll just get more and more stowaways.
I think we'll lock you up in the brig
below deck until we make it to port.
Hey, Captain.
I'd like to ask you something.
You verified the identities of
all ten men on board, haven't you?
Of course, they're all veterans.
Each one of them on this
ship for over ten years.
I'll vouch for every single man
I'm not sure why you're
so worried about that
since I gave you my word
from the very beginning.
Oh, by the way
I must request that you not
smoke on deck What were you
planning on doing with the ash
and butt after you were done?
Were you just going to toss
them into these pristine waters?
You may be a guest on this ship,
but you will abide by my rules.
You got that?
You got it, kid?
Hold it, Pops.
If you don't want me to smoke
aboard ship, then just tell me.
Don't be a condescending prick
about the whole thing, you jackass.
Hey, Jotaro, don't be
disrespectful to the captain.
You're the one at fault.
His rules don't mean shit.
I'll be as rude as I want.
And you know why?
The captain is the stand user.
What the?
A stand user?
I'm not sure I follow you.
What is that?
That is completely impossible, Jotaro.
We chose Captain Dragon
because he came recommended
with verification by the
Speedwagon Foundation.
He's someone that we can trust.
There's no chance that he's a stand user.
Hold on, what's this thing, a stand?
I've no idea what you
guys are talking about.
Jojo, random guesses will only
make things more confusing!
Do you have any real proof, Jojo?
I've found a way to differentiate
stand users from others.
What?
The trick is to watch a possible Stan user
around cigarette smoke
because a single whiff!
Makes a vein pop up on their nose?
What the hell are they all doing
you're not serious Jotaro relax.
I'm lying That said it looks
like we found the idiot didn't we
Quite impressive, but what tipped
you off that it was the captain?
Actually, I really didn't have a clue.
However, I'd planned to try this with the
entire crew from the moment we arrived.
Simple as that.
And I fell for it.
Didn't expect this, but damn, you're good.
You're right, I'm not the captain.
The real captain's already sleeping with
the fissures at the
bottom of the China Sea.
If that's true, then you can sleep
in the depths of hell, you bastard!
Dammit, no!
Let me go, I can't move!
Trouble on the water, lies in betrayal.
The moon card represents
the fear of the unknown.
Its name, Dark Blue Moon.
I kept my identity hidden
hoping to pick you off one by
one five on one is so troublesome
even for me the other way
would have been much simpler
but since you've figured me
out I have no choice five on
one it is getting my hands on
her just shows that lady
luck is on my side think I'll
take a dip in these shark
infested waters with a rut if you
want to save her you're gonna
have to dive in after us in
the ocean I have the advantage
I can take on all five of you.
Go on.
Act tough while you hide behind a hostage.
It'll take a lot more than that
to shake me up, you dumbass.
It's no act.
This is a prediction.
I hear your Stanstar Platinum is fast.
I'd like to put that to the test.
I'm not trying to brag, but my
dark blue moon is king underwater.
It's much swifter than
any fish in the sea,
and certainly faster than
a vulgar meathead like you.
Why don't we test them out right now?
Come on, follow me if you're not
afraid of a little saltwater!
He attacked me faster than we could fall.
That's impossible for a human. How'd he...
You're the only one who's
swallowing salt water today, Pops.
Choke on it. Tell him, Avdol.
Your folly was trying to
out-predict a fortune teller.
Tough break.
Well said, Avdol.
There he goes.
He talked up his stance power
so much I expected more,
but in the end he was
just a blabbering idiot.
What's the matter, Jotaro?
Hurry and pull the girl
out already, would ya?
What's wrong?
Do you need a hand with her?
Damn it!
I'm being pulled in!
Look, those are...
They're barnacles.
They're a type of crustacean that
lives between high and low tides.
They're on Star Platinum's arm, and they've
got him stuck to the side of the boat!
He's still got some fight left in him.
He must have attached them
when I hit him before.
Damn things keep multiplying.
My stand strength, it's being drained.
The captain's disappeared.
I can't see him in the water anymore.
Jotaro, pull in your stand right now.
What do you think I'm trying to do?
That's why I'm sweating like
a freaking pig, old man.
Hurrah! Jojo!
Jojo!
He fell in! We've...
we've gotta...
Hurrah!
Welcome, landlubber.
Glad you could join me
in the watery depths.
It's where dark blue moon reigns
supreme, the undersea realm.
Bad idea to underestimate me, brother.
Could be deadly.
Since we can talk underwater
through our stands,
how about you pop out another one of
those cocky one-liners before you die?
What's the matter?
Catfish got your tongue, brother?
So, what would you like
after I'm done with you? Huh?
It would be a shame to
weigh such fresh fish.
Fish paste?
Maybe a plate of sashimi?
I'll make one hell of a
meal out of your stand.
Don't play games with me.
You're trying to sound tough,
but I know the truth, boy.
The real terror of all this is
starting to sink into your thick skull.
I can even tell what you're thinking.
How long can he stay underwater?
I can probably last about two minutes,
but can he last longer than me?
Am I right, brother?
Let me answer you.
My lung capacity is three
times that of a normal human's.
See, for years I've been training.
Six minutes and 12 seconds
is my best submerged time.
You must be dizzy just hearing
that number, right, brother?
And...
Dark Blue Moon's fins are cutters that
move faster than a ship's propeller,
far sharper too.
Before you get overconfident again,
you might want to take a
good hard look at your stand.
Seems Dark Blue Moon's
barnacles have taken
a liking to absorbing your stand's power.
How does it feel to have your life energy
slowly draining away from your body?
Trying to run away by swimming back up?
Take a good look around you!
Haven't you realized, brother, Dark Blue
Moon has created an underwater whirlpool?
There's no way you can possibly
escape! That's right! Swim faster!
You'll just make it harder to breathe
while your power keeps draining!
But it's a little too early to kill a
stupid, smart-ass punk like you just yet!
It's been too long!
He's still not coming up!
A giant whirlpool!
It must have him trapped!
Where the hell is Jojo?
Let's go and save him.
These are scales.
That guy's stand has
scales as sharp as razors.
There are countless scales
swirling in that whirlpool.
He wasn't bluffing when he said he
could beat all five of us at once.
It's like a watery antlion pit.
If we dive in, it's very possible
we'll be sliced to pieces.
His scales?
I'll take another guess
at what you're thinking.
In a whirlpool, only one spot stays still.
Such mundane logic.
It's the eye.
If I jump into the center
where he is, I can attack him.
That's what you're thinking, right?
If you believe you can hit me
with that punch of yours again,
Then come and give it a shot.
Throw your worthless stand at me.
Its power's so drained
it doesn't have a chance.
See if you can manage an attack,
one that's even sharper than
these underwater cutters.
I'm waiting, brother!
Damn him!
We're completely helpless!
It's Jojo!
I just saw Jojo in the whirlpool. Buddha!
I don't think he's moving down there.
So he went limp?
He wasn't struggling
against the whirlpool?
Oh, well, that might
actually be a good thing.
Weren't you gonna turn
me into sashimi boy?
You're the one who's gonna be sliced up!
Starfinger!
Sorry, did I interrupt you?
Who's going to be sashimi?
What's that?
I can't hear you.
You're going to have to speak up.
We're underwater.
But your power was being drained.
You let yourself go live
on purpose, didn't you?
You concentrated your
power in your fingers.
That's what you were thinking all along.
Not even close.
The only thing on my mind
is how gross it'll be
when I kick your stupid ass and
you piss yourself under water.
And that's all.
Bye, pups.
Jojo!
That's my grandson for ya.
Well done, Jotaro.
Hurry and come-a-her!
That captain planted some
bombs after all! Damn it!
Send out a distress call!
Here, you should have some water.
We've sent out distress calls,
so someone should be here with
a rescue ship soon enough.
Okay, just what the hell is going on here?
I don't get any of this.
Who are you guys?
Just think of us as fellow travelers.
You're on a journey to see your father,
while I'm on one for my daughter.
Hey, that's the only fresh water we have.
So don't spit it out.
We need it.
No, no.
No!
Everyone look there! Mm-hmm.
Huh?
All the old paintings on the tomb.
They do the sand dance, don't you know?
If they move too quick!
They're falling down like a domino.
All the birds are men by the Nile.
They've got their money on a bed.
Called crocodiles.
They snap their teeth on your cigarette.
Foreign types with a hookah. I say.
Walk like an Egyptian.
The blonde waitresses take their trays.
Spin around and they cross the floor.
They've got the moves, oh-hey-oh?
You drop your drink,
then they bring you more.
All the school kids so sick of books,
they're like the punk and the metal band.
When the buzzer rings, they're
walking like an Egyptian.
All the kids in the marketplace say,
Walk like an Egyptian.
I can't find a single
sign of human life aboard.
I feel sticky from the salt water.
This is what it means
to face death, damn ape.
Thinks he's won already.